const easy = [{
        "question": "How many infinity stones are there in the Marvel Universe?",
        "choices": ["10", "6", "3", "8"],
        "correct": "6"
    },

    {
        "question": "What is the name of the cube that Loki utilizes to power up his weapons?",
        "choices": ["Tetracube", "Trimurti", "Trimeric", "Tesseract"],
        "correct": "Tesseract"
    },

    {
        "question": "Which country is the birthplace of Black Widow?",
        "choices": ["Canada", "America", "South Africa", "Russia"],
        "correct": "Russia"
    },

    {
        "question": "What was the first movie that started the Marvel Cinematic Universe?",
        "choices": ["Iron Man", "The Incredible Hulk", "Captain America: The First Avenger", "Thor"],
        "correct": "Iron Man"
    },

    {
        "question": "Who was able to pick up Thor's sword in Avengers: Endgame?",
        "choices": ["Hulk", "Captain America", "Captain Marvel", "Spiderman"],
        "correct": "Captain America"
    },

    {
        "question": "What is Thor's ax's name that was created for him in Avengers: Infinity War?",
        "choices": ["Heartbreaker", "Windbreaker", "Stormbreaker", "Mj√∂lnir"],
        "correct": "Stormbreaker"
    },

    {
        "question": "Who is the first person that turns to dust in Avengers: Infinity War?",
        "choices": ["Falcon", "Bucky", "Groot", "Black Panther"],
        "correct": "Bucky"
    },

    {
        "question": "What's the name of Tony Stark's company?",
        "choices": ["Stark Enterprise", "Stark Worldwide", "Stark Industries", "Stark Superheroes"],
        "correct": "Stark Industries"
    },

    {
        "question": "What is T'Challa's sister's name?",
        "choices": ["Shari", "Shaba", "Shami", "Shuri"],
        "correct": "Shuri"
    },

    {
        "question": "Who is the main antagonist in the first Avengers movie?",
        "choices": ["Thanos", "Ego", "Abomination", "Loki"],
        "correct": "Loki"
    }
];

const medium = [{
        "question": "Who is the brother of Scarlet Witch?",
        "choices": ["Quicksilver", "Mercury", "Cobalt", "Aluminium"],
        "correct": "Quicksilver"
    },

    {
        "question": "In which MCU movie did Spiderman first appear?",
        "choices": ["Avengers: Infinity War", "Ant-Man", "Spider-Man: Homecoming", "Captain America: Civil War"],
        "correct": "Captain America: Civil War"
    },

    {
        "question": "Who is the head of S.H.I.E.L.D?",
        "choices": ["Phil Coulson", "Nick Fury", "Clint Barton", "Sharon Carter"],
        "correct": "Nick Fury"
    },

    {
        "question": "Who did Captain America fall in love with?",
        "choices": ["Pepper Potts", "Peggy Carter", "May Barker", "Wanda Maximoff"],
        "correct": "Peggy Carter"
    },

    {
        "question": "What does Stan Lee cameo as in Guardians of the Galaxy Vol. 2?",
        "choices": ["Quill's farther", "A Ravager", "An Astronaut", "A Krylorian"],
        "correct": "An Astronaut"
    },

    {
        "question": "In Loki, what does the TVA stand for?",
        "choices": ["Tesseract Viability Access", "Time Variant Access", "Time Variant Authority", "Thor Visits Asgard"],
        "correct": "Time Variant Authority"
    },

    {
        "question": "What was Scott Lang Arrested for?",
        "choices": ["Burglary", "Arson", "Criminal Damage", "Fraud"],
        "correct": "Burglary"
    },

    {
        "question": "Which of the following actors hasn't played The Hulk?",
        "choices": ["Mark Ruffalo", "Edward Norton", "Eric Bana", "Henry Cavill"],
        "correct": "Henry Cavill"
    },

    {
        "question": "How old is Thor revealed to be in Avengers: Infinity War?",
        "choices": ["150", "1,500", "36", "3012"],
        "correct": "1,500"
    },

    {
        "question": "\"With great power comes great responsibility\" is said by which character?",
        "choices": ["Uncle Ben", "Frigga", "Captain America", "Bruce Banner"],
        "correct": "Uncle Ben"
    },
];

const hard = [{
        "question": "Who kills Aunt May in Spider-Man: No Way Home?",
        "choices": ["Dr Octopus", "Electro", "Lizard", "Green Goblin"],
        "correct": "Green Goblin"
    },

    {
        "question": "What is the name of the Hippopotamus goddes in Moon Knight?",
        "choices": ["Bastet", "Amunet", "Tawaret", "Hathor"],
        "correct": "Tawaret"
    },

    {
        "question": "In which year was the first Marvel Comic released?",
        "choices": ["1998", "1963", "1971", "1939"],
        "correct": "1939"
    },

    {
        "question": "How many years was Steve Rogers trapped under the ice?",
        "choices": ["5", "28", "87", "66"],
        "correct": "66"
    },

    {
        "question": "Which infinity stone do the Guardians have to save in Guardians of the Galaxy Vol. 1?",
        "choices": ["The Soul Stone", "The Power Stone", "The Reality Stone", "The Mind Stone"],
        "correct": "The Power Stone"
    },

    {
        "question": "What is the name of the dwarf who made Thanos's gauntlet?",
        "choices": ["Tyrion", "Trumpkin", "Eitri", "Finbar"],
        "correct": "Eitri"
    },

    {
        "question": "Which of these isn't made of Vibranium?",
        "choices": ["Vision", "Mjolnir", "Bucky's Arm", "Captain America's Shield"],
        "correct": "Mjolnir"
    },

    {
        "question": "What is Pepper Potts allergic to?",
        "choices": ["Pepper", "Shellfish", "Strawberries", "Nuts"],
        "correct": "Strawberries"
    },

    {
        "question": "Who isn't a member of The Warriors Three?",
        "choices": ["Heimdal", "Fandral", "Hogun", "Volstaag"],
        "correct": "Heimdal"
    },

    {
        "question": "Stan Lee made his final cameo in which Marvel movie?",
        "choices": ["Guardians of the Galaxy Vol 2", "Avengers: Infinity War", "Thor: The Dark World", "Avengers: End Game"],
        "correct": "Avengers: End Game"
    },
];